

10429 Washington Blvd NE, Blaine, MN 55434 (651) 675-8655 ConOfTheDev@gmail.com www.LinkedIn.com/in/don-vo/

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

I am a full-stack software engineer with over six years of industry experience specializing in web development, Agile methodology, quality assurance testing, and automated testing. Adept at collaborating with multiple teams, adapting to new technologies, and maintaining clean, readable code. Values code quality, automated testing, and application accessibility.

EXPERIENCE

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

Software Engineer / Beech Valley Solutions, Atlanta, GA (Remote)

- Implement front-end and back-end features for a staffing web application geared towards Certified Public Accountants, Auditors, Advisors, and more
 - Develop a new applicant system that allows internal users to view and manage potential consultants using React, TypeScript, CSS, GraphQL, Node.js, and PostgreSQL
 - o Produce several Slack automations using TypeScript, Node.js and Slack API for user interactions in the application to provide internal users visibility on applicants and consultants
 - Create email automations for clients to provide updates on applicants they are interested in using TypeScript and Node.js
 - Modernize a Postgres-backed search to use ElasticSearch, greatly increasing performance while adding new capabilities such as full-text resume search
- Add custom continuous integration functionality to automatically mark stories as complete in our project management system as soon as they are deployed to production
- Collaborate with internal users to implement tools and features that improve their workflow
- Provide application support to internal users for application issues encountered
- Ensure high code quality by writing automated tests using Jest and participating in code reviews
- Gave product demos to the entire company to educate the team on new features

JULY 2020 - MARCH 2022

Software Engineer II / Infinite Campus, Blaine, MN

- Implemented front-end and back-end features for multiple, diverse products designed for teachers and office administrators in K-12 school districts across the United States
 - Created features to simplify the user experience, such as managing field trips and after school activities, using HTML, Sass, TypeScript, Java and SQL
 - Produced back-end functionality to parse and convert curriculum from IMS Common Cartridge standards to be functional with existing features in the product using Java and SQL
 - Developed curriculum search features for teachers to find imported curriculum using HTML, Sass,
 TypeScript, and Java
- Wrote and maintain unit and API tests for codebase using Jest, Spock, and Cypress
- Managed and lead sprint planning

AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2020

Software Engineer / Infinite Campus, Blaine, MN

• Implemented front-end and back-end features for a web application designed for office administrators to run payrolls and manage time off requests

- Completed web pages for creating and managing pay codes, deduction codes, pay periods, benefits, and for running payrolls using HTML, Sass, TypeScript, Java, and SQL
- Created several report generators for time off requests, payment breakdowns, and amounts paid out per pay period using SSRS
- Collaborated with other teams to provide reusable components for consistency across all products
- Wrote and maintain unit and API tests for codebase using Jest, Spock, and Protractor
- Managed and led sprint planning and retrospective

MARCH 2017 - AUGUST 2017

Software Engineer Intern / Infinite Campus, Blaine, MN

- Implemented front-end features for a web application designed for office administrators to manage and store employee job information and associated documents
 - o Developed a personnel report generator for a large teacher retirement system using SSRS
- Fixed bugs using a proprietary language based on XSLT

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Pokémon Go Raid Bot / github.com/rytrex/raidio

• Designed and created a Discord bot for manually reporting upcoming and active raids in Pokémon Go and providing useful information to help players with the raid using TypeScript, Node.js, and Discord.js

Pomodoro for Habitica / github.com/rytrex/PomodoroForHabitica

Developed a stand-alone web page with a pomodoro timer which automatically updates a Habitica habit at the end
of the timer using Angular and Habitica's API

PROFICIENCIES

- Languages: TypeScript, Javascript, SQL, Java, GraphQL, HTML5, CSS, Sass, Python, Terraform, Groovy, C, XSLT
- Frameworks: React, Angular, Protractor, Cypress, Hibernate, Jersey, Objection
- Libraries: Kendo UI for Angular, Tailwind, React Table, Material UI
- **Technical**: Git, Agile Scrum, Kanban, ElasticSearch, Node.js, Continuous Integration, Continuous Deployment, Kubernetes, Docker

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2013 - APRIL 2017

Bachelors of Science, Computer Science and Mathematics / Augsburg College, Minneapolis, MN

• National Honor Society: Pi Mu Epsilon